OPPORTUNITY COST. Every choice has a hidden trade-off.
CHOOSE A = GIVE UP B. The best alternative you give up is the opportunity cost.
MOMO CAN ONLY CHOOSE ONE. Fish now, or playtime first?
WHAT MOMO GIVES UP. Choosing the fish means giving up playtime.
COMFORT VS GROWTH. A nap has value. Learning has value too.
YOUR DAILY CHOICES. Time, money, attention, and energy all have trade-offs.
MOMO’S 3-STEP METHOD. Choose clearly. Compare the best alternative. Think long-term.
PAUSE BEFORE YOU CHOOSE. A three-second pause can change the decision.
BETTER ORDER, BETTER OUTCOME. Sometimes the best choice is changing the sequence.
NEXT: SUPPLY & DEMAND. Subscribe for Episode 2.